Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vanice-nguyen-2749a114b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Change Management
Microsoft Office
Human Resources Information
Systems (HRIS)

Certifications

Excel for Project Management
Performing under Pressure
Human Resources in the OnDemand Economy
Managing Your Manager
Strategic Human Resources

Vanice Nguyen

HR Business Partner

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced HRBP Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the financial services industry. Skilled in Negotiation, HR Consulting, HR Policies, Employee Relations and Teamwork. Strong human resources professional with a Bachelor of Business Administration focused in Business Administration and Management, General from Ho Chi Minh City University of Foreign Languages - Information Technology.

Experience

NAM A BANK HR Business Partner April 2022 - Present (3 years)

VSHR Pro Academy Recruitment Consultant September 2022 - November 2022 (3 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

VSHR Career Service Career Advisor September 2022 - November 2022 (3 months) We find amazing people to change company's future

Orient Commercial Joint Stock Bank (OCB)
2 years 3 months
HRBP Manager
March 2020 - April 2021 (1 year 2 months)

Senior Human Resources Specialist February 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Sacombank
Human Resources Executive

June 2011 - June 2018 (7 years 1 month)

Vietnam

Education

Ho Chi Minh City University of Foreign Languages - Information Technology

Bachelor of Business Administration, Business Administration and Management, General